Tom Miller papers, 1852-2003 (Bulk 1950-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VI: Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Ramparts (Pt.2), 1971-1972 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Ramparts Wall Poster, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Rat! Subterranean News, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Realist (Pt.1), 1961-1996 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Realist (Pt.2), 1961-1996 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Realist (Pt.3), 1961-1996 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Realist(Pt.4), 1961-1996 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Realist, The Last Supplement to the Whole Earth Catalog, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera – Red Earth, No date (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Recuerden El Alamo, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Rep Papers 3, No date (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Red Raider, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Reliable Source, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The Reporter, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Richard Gary Chandler, "This Man is Dangerous", Mad Funk, No date (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Rip Off Comics, 1978-1989 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Rockers, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Salt of the Earth, No date (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Scanlan's, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -The Schools Must Serve the People (SDS), No date (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -SDS, An Introduction, No date (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -SDS, New Left Notes, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Seven Days, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Shaft, 1960-1967 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Skull Comics, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Slow Death, 1976-1977 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Southern Student Organization Committee. Prospectus, 1967-1968 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Space City, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Street Sheets Greatest Hits, No date (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Student As Nigger, No date (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Takeover, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Tasty Comics, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Thank You Lil' Dick, YIP Non-leaders, No date (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -They Did Bust Our Music, No date (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - A Thithle Thampler, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Time and Place to be Annouced, Yippie, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -To Our Greek Brothers and Sisters, Athenian Alliance, No date (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Truck Down to Georgetown, DC. YIP Communiqué, Nodate (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - The True Selma Story, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Underground Press Review, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Underground Press Syndicate Members, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Unmasking the Civil Rights Bill, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Up from Under, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -U.P.S. Directory, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Washington Free Press, 1968-1969 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -When Southern Labor Stirs, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - White Comanche, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - White Panther Party, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Who Put the Bomp, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Who's Where, College of Wooster Directory, 1967-1968 (Box 59, Folder 45)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Whore! (Bridal Fair), Women for Equal Treatment, No date (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Willamette Bridge, No date (Box 59, Folder 47)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Win, 1971-1974 (Box 59, Folder 48)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Wooster Voice (Pt. 1), 1966-1968 (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Wooster Voice (Pt. 2), 1967 (Box 59, Folder 50)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Wooster Voice (Pt. 3), 1967-1968 (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Workers World, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -YIR Events of the Week, No date (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -YIP, Ten Days To Change the World, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -YIPL, unitdate>1972 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Yippie, The Last of the Big Protest Demonstrations, No date (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Yipster Times, 1975-1977 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -You are Charged with a Felony (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -You Can't Jail the Revolution, No date (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera - Young Lust, 1977-1980 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera -Youth International Party Manifesto (Box 60, Folder 10)